It's open. Come in.
Rohan-sensei?
Where are you?
Over here, Koichi.
Rohan-sensei!
Why are you in the corner?
When you asked me over here, you
didn't say you were in panic mode!
Please, Koichi, I need your help.
I'm in the grasp of an
enemy's stand. What?
A stand's in here? Where
is it? What's it do?
It's over here.
Damn thing adhered itself to my back.
It did what?
So you're saying there's a
stand attached to your back?
That's right.
It's a very serious dilemma.
And I don't know what to do.
Can I see what we're dealing with?
No way.
But if you don't show it to
me, how am I supposed to...
If I expose my back, it'll
kill me and take hold of you.
Now burn the pages. Yes. Hear that?
Even as we speak, it's
whispering in my ear.
You're not making sense!
Wait, this is all some big
joke at my expense, isn't it?
How could you say that?
I just told you if I expose
my back, I'm done for!
Oh, I heard you, but how do I know you're
not pulling my leg like you always do?
Ugh...
Hit the nail on the head, didn't I?
No, I'm being completely serious!
There's a dead body upstairs!
What?!
A real dead body?!
So, uh...
What are you doing, Rohan-sensei?
Don't worry about that,
just bow on past me.
Please, Koichi, you have to see the body.
Get going!
Can you tell me what all this is about?
Told you.
I'm telling the truth.
It's gone.
How did it just disappear?
Look, Koichi, he's there.
You see? It's the man.
This is Masazo Kinoto.
After he died, he turned
into a lifeless husk.
Wow, that's some really impressive work.
Nice job.
But this isn't the time
to be messing around.
I know you know that.
While I'm with you,
those stand users the old man and the
photo made are trying to hunt us down.
The only reason I rushed
all the way over here was
because I was worried
something happened to you.
Why won't you?
Wait, the stand.
Anyway, just be careful.
Bye.
Hold on, Koichi, don't leave!
I asked you to come here
because I knew those pieces of
shit Josuke and Okuyasu would
just laugh at my predicament!
You have to trust me, I
thought we were friends!
Keicho!
Cheer up, bucko, yes.
Disappointment's just
another part of life.
This is infuriating.
I've never been so thoroughly humiliated.
Bastard, you're going to pay dearly.
Let's go.
It's the light of the sun,
and it's the light of the light.
Let the voice of love take you higher.
It's the power of the stars.
It's the light
of the light.
My nails are going through their
signature growth spurt again,
and it's no wonder why.
The way your hands run through that
perfectly coiffed hair is just...
Consider yourself lucky.
You've nearly escaped death.
At least until I fully
transitioned to Kosaku Kawajiri.
My old man's such a pest.
I can't leave the house without
the Cursed Kodger following me.
I even caught him spying on me once.
Maybe he thinks you're
out partying too much.
And whose fault would it be if I was?
I was so pissed at him,
I decided to freak him out by shoplifting
right in front of his saggy face.
Then I made a beeline to your
place, which I'm sure set him off.
You're insane, girl.
The cops are probably after you right now.
Ugh.
Hey, you.
What's the big idea
touching people's bags?
What's wrong?
Forget it, baby.
It's not worth our time.
The hell?
You a pervert?
Or just a damn pickpocket?
Mariah! Mariah!
Oh, shit, babe.
Look, we're already in Mariah.
Come on, let's go.
Ow! That freaking hurt!
What the hell is your deal?
Watch it where you're walking, jerk-off.
You see what he was carrying?
It was a bowling pin nail clipper.
What kind of breed carries
around something like that?
Can you say lame?
You've got the pictures, yes?
Where do you think you're going with them?
To the Mariah Grand Hotel.
I've no other choice.
You're going to Jotaro?
He won't be able to help you.
Your best bet is to call it
quits and burn the pictures.
Impressive!
And all while someone could have
been watching from a window.
That was very risky.
There, you see?
At some point, almost every
street comes to an intersection.
See?
Someone will take a peek at your
back, so crossing's impossible!
And since the road is about to
get wider, that means more people!
Let's stop all this and go back, yes?
You're never going to
make it across the road!
You really think so?
Masazo Kinoto made it
to my house, didn't he?
He'd have had to have crossed
an intersection to do so.
I'm sure I can pull it off, too.
I just need to know how he did it.
Aha! Like this!
This certainly isn't my most shining
moment, but it'll get me across.
Not bad, Rohan Kishibe.
But there's something you
haven't thought about.
When Masazo Kinoto was crossing the street,
I stayed as quiet as a church mouse!
Hey, dumb shit!
Why are you farting along like some slug?
What did you just say?
See?
Yo, why don't you turn
around and find out?
You're pushing it.
The only one who's missing
something here, Cheap Trap, is you.
I have something Masazo didn't.
My stand, heaven's door!
What the?! Perfect.
Now that that's settled, I
can get to the other side.
I suggest you prepare yourself. Say what?
What's going on here?
Trust me, you'll never make it!
When this is over, you'll be a
shriveled up limp dick of a corpse!
You sure talk a good game, but
that's all you're good at, isn't it?
You won't be saying anything soon.
WHO THE HELL DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE TALKING TO, BITCH?!
What? Huh?
It seems there won't be any
major intersections for a while.
Hey, do you know if your heaven's door
works on animals? Huh? Huh? Do ya?
Yes, it works on any intelligent
animal. Well, in that case,
if an animal sees your back, it stands to
reason I'll be able to transfer to them!
Much easier than people, yes?
That's right, I'll have to be
just as careful around them.
God, I hate these creatures.
Their glare is infuriating.
Oh, right cat, beat it!
How in the...
they're swarming!
All it takes is a quick glance from
any one of these little guys, yes?
You were right when you said the only
thing I'm good at is talking, yes.
But humans aren't the only
living things I can talk to!
Bingo!
I summoned those animals here!
And they are not happy givers!
I just finished telling them that
you love killing cats and dogs!
So imagine what they think!
Sick 'em, buds!
Heaven's door!
It's no use!
There are too many of them!
Yes, I win!
Three, freeze!
These animals didn't do anything wrong.
Time to get lost, all of you. Shoo!
That sound belongs to...
Keicho! What?
I thought you were fooling me like always?
but I had this nagging feeling,
so I went back to your house and
found you acting just as weird.
Even when you got outside, you were
still skulking around the sidewalk?
with your back against the wall.
Then there's how you crossed the road.
You were telling the truth about
the stand stuck to your back.
This is why I admire you.
You're the real deal, Koichi.
A true blue friend to the
very end. It's on your back.
So all we have to do is remove that
parasite and we're good to go, right?
Reverb!
Special Ability 3! Freeze!
Miss Force!
You did it!
It's not that easy.
I'm clinging to you with my special
ability and not brute strength.
If you try to rip me off, you'll just end
up destroying your back in the process.
Now tell Koichi, yes?
Come on, you better hurry and spit it out.
What, Rohan-sensei?
I'm grateful to you, Koichi.
The fact that you would help
me has truly touched my heart.
but I'd appreciate it if
you'd withdraw act three.
You can't see it from there,
but it would seem my back is
starting to rip itself open.
Act three, withdraw three
frees on the double.
S-H-I-T, withdraw completed.
Hey, you okay, Rohan sensei?
How bad is it?
How bad does it look, Koichi Hirose?
You're the reason he's in this mess.
Understand now, Rohan,
you can't remove me.
You can try to tear me
off by force if you want,
but you'll end up tearing off
your own back along the way!
Hey, you're just going
to exhaust yourself.
I wonder, will you collapse
from the trauma and fatigue?
Or will you go insane and kill yourself?
Even the most powerful
stan in the world couldn't
beat this weaklings gift for
gab and utter domination!
Yes!
A stan that clings to backs!
This is too bizarre!
Bizarre. So true. Have a look.
You know you want to.
Do it.
I'm happy to give you a peek.
He's finally lost his mind!
Now you realize a visit
to Jotaro would be futile!
Jotaro?
I never had any intention
of ever paying him a visit.
This was my destination.
I was beside myself
that I finally made it.
I can't help but laugh.
What's with all the rambling?
You finally exposed your
back to another soul!
Now I get to pass into Koichi Hirose!
Wait!
I know this street!
This is where we met!
Cheap trap, you picked a hell
of a place to turn around.
Even if you had known about this
place and resisted turning around,
you would have still had no
choice but to look Koichi's way?
thanks to your special ability.
What the hell?
We're walking down Rainy Street!
Looking back's a death wish!
You were right about no stand being
able to remove you from my back.
You'd just end up hurting me if you tried.
However, there is something
that can take you.
Something that latches on to
those who dare to look back.
Something that'll carry
away your very soul.
Let me go!
Please let me go, yes!
Where are these things gonna take me?
Answer!
To the other side.
I can't say for sure whether
there's a heaven or a hell,
but a simple memo should do the trick.
For a stand that does nothing but talk,
he was quite a little terror, Koichi.
If you hadn't have shown up when you did,
I'm sure I wouldn't still
be around to tell the tale.
I had no clue this is where we ended up.
I was too focused on
that freaky enemy stand.
It's Reimi.
Hey, Rohan.
Did you take these pictures? Yes. Why?
Check this out.
How strange.
Did you hear?
Mika got her boyfriend to buy her a
brand new pair of designer earrings.
What do you say you buy me some?
Maybe next time.
The hell you think you're doing, skis?
You can't come in here!
Get out of my apartment!
Hmm, a studio apartment.
My name is Yoshikage Kira.
Would you be so kind as
to tell me your name?
They don't look normal, do they?
Look how long they've gotten.
Do you think there's a single soul on the
planet who can keep
their nails from growing?
There isn't.
No one can stop a nail's destiny to grow.
Just as there's no one who can truly
suppress the inner passions one is born with.
Now, I believe I asked
you to tell me your name.
What did you do to my boyfriend?
He was right here before...
Don't ever answer a
question with a question!
You did learn proper etiquette while
you were in school now, didn't you?
I'm asking you to tell
me what your name is!
Minako!
My name is Minako!
Minako.
What a beautiful name your
parents bestowed upon you.
I approve.
Minako I have a little request if
you don't mind I would be thrilled if
you could hold on to these for me and
I'd greatly appreciate it if you could
trim my robust nails with these lame
clippers you've never done this before
have you it's your lucky day now don't
cut them too short someone help me?
I'm sorry!
Forgive me! Forgive you?
Now, wait just a minute.
I'm not the least bit angry if
that's what's concerning you.
You intrigue me.
I chose you because of our connection.
I was born with a certain set of desires,
so I simply try to make the most of it.
Life's better that way.
You were begging your boyfriend
for a pair of earrings, yeah?
He left these for you.
What do you think?
You truly are a deft nail-cutter.
How I adore you.
I dare say you're even
cuter when you're silent.
So what to do now, my dear?
I'd love to take you back home with me.
But I don't think the
Kawajiris would approve.
Oh, how I've missed the sensation.
I feel so complete.
So that man and woman he
followed here from the station,
he completely vaporized them.
What?
That's Hayato.
What could he be doing here?
This is in the opposite direction
from the house and school.
What's that?
Damn it, I forgot to lock the door.
Could Hayato have?
It couldn't be.
There's no way he's human.
Why is that demon pretending to be my dad?
This might be evidence that he's returned.
I'm pretty sure this is blood.
So Kira's finally made his move.
I'm absolutely positive.
Hayato is holding a
video camera in his hand.
It doesn't seem to be
anywhere in his room.
I've definitely noticed
Hayato acting strange lately.
What is that boy up to?
I have to find out.
I need to know for sure.
I have to calm down. Breathe, Hayato.
Just calm down and gather your thoughts.
First, I need to deal with this tape.
Should I show it to someone?
It can't be Mom.
She has complete and
total faith in the guy.
Should I show it to the police?
Would they believe that I witnessed a
man being vaporized right in front of me?
What am I saying?
He's not a normal human!
Could the police even
catch someone like him?
Is there anyone in the world who has what
it takes to catch a monster like him?
What do I do?
Sooner or later, he's
gonna kill Mom and me.
What am I gonna do?
Evening.
Is there any room in there left for me?
Can dear old dad join you?
Why the odd face?
We've done this before.
Oh, I was actually just
finishing up and...
Don't be silly.
I am your father.
We should do some bonding.
What's he planning to do?
If he finds this tape, it's all over.
Sorry to be a bother, but I'll need
to use that bucket for the bath. Huh?
I'd like to wash the long
day away with some water.
No!
Since we're bonding, I'll
wash your bath for you, Dad!
Hmm?
What a splendid idea.
But, please allow me to
wash your back first.
You've been in the bath for
a while, so it's only fair.
We can just take turns.
How does that sound?
Here, sit.
What is it?
You're sweating like a guilty
little pig ripe for slaughter.
or did the heat get to you?
No, I'm fine.
Just look at the way you're shaking.
You can't be fine.
It'd be rather odd for a person to tremble
after being in the bath for too long.
He cut it out there!
The tickles!
You can't touch my back
there because I freak out!
I've only told you a million times!
How silly of me. You're right.
You always were a ticklish one, Hayato.
I'll take care of the front myself.
I'd be happy to lend you a hand.
By the way, I wanted to
talk to you about something.
This evening,
I was doing some work errands in the
opposite end of town near Jozenji,
when I happened to see you.
And you were holding a video camera.
What could you have been doing there?
I've got him.
I knew this sleuthing
shit was spying on me.
I can't believe it.
So much for casually
assimilating into this family.
It has been one catastrophe after another.
A year of hell.
Killing this punk will cause a
commotion, and a bad one at that.
But he saw everything.
I have no choice.
A strand of this brat's hair
now functions as a bomb.
All it'll take is a
small blast to his skull,
and it'll appear he simply
slipped and bumped his head.
People slip and fall in
the bathroom all the time.
So it's time for you to die past
so you're gonna kill me, too
Take a look around pops.
I'm recording everything that's happening
I've never trusted you. fraud!
I've recorded all your weird shoe sizes
and signature practice accessions.
And that's not all!
I taped that cat plant
living in the attic, too?
Only I know where all the tapes are, but
if something terrible were to happen to me,
I'm sure someone would
find them eventually.
Where do you get off?
You're not gonna lay a finger on me!
We clear?
How dare you?
You think you could
threaten the likes of me?
And that goes double for Mom!
Break it down.
Break out.